Hey Damian, thanks for taking the time
today.
>> Hey, how you doing man?
>> We'll kick it off with Ed and then we'll
go to Dave.
Oh, I don't know what that was. Uh,
sorry about that, Damian. Um, I just,
um, I want to ask you, can first of all,
welcome to Philadelphia and and then,
uh, secondly, why Philadelphia when you
look at this running back room and it
has someone like Saquon Barkley in it?
>> I think that's one of the the better
reason to choose this room, you know, a
great guy who's done a incredible job
and every year he's played in this
league, you know, whether it's here,
whether it's in New York, like his
entire career, he's been a great running
back and that's a great guy to be around
and learn from.
We'll go to Dave and then John.
>> Hey Damian, how do you view your career
so far? You got off to such a hot start
in Houston. I know that it probably
hasn't gone the way you'd like after
that.
>> Come again, please.
>> I How do you view your career so far? I
know you got off to such a hot start in
Houston as a rookie and then after that,
I'm sure it probably hasn't gone the way
you expected.
>> Oh, you said how do I view it?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, man. It's still a career. You know,
I'm still learning. you know, coming
into this year, I have I just look at it
as I got four years experience on my
side. You know, I take every up and down
in my career in my career as a
collective and um just look at it and
try to learn how to get better from it.
You know, coming to Philly is just
another step in my journey that I'm
looking forward to and um at the end of
the day, man, I just want to play ball
and um Philly gave me a a great
opportunity to do so.
>> We'll go to John and then Jeff.
>> Hey, Damian. Uh welcome to Philly. Um it
your rookie year I think you had your
careerhigh against the Eagles. Uh what
what do you remember about that game and
and um do you think uh you can get back
to that point?
>> What I remember specifically about that
game is Thursday night lights, baby. One
of the biggest games I played in. It was
a fun game in front of a great crowd
against a great team. Unfortunately, you
know, at that time we couldn't pull it
out, but uh I'm with the Eagles now, so
I'm just going to focus on that. But,
uh, as far as the second part of your
question, of course, you know, that's
always the goal, you know, try to get
back to the high level of football and
just do whatever I can for the team I'm
at now. And, um, at this time is the
Philadelphia Eagles and, um, we're going
to work towards that.
>> We'll go to Jeff and then Rub.
>> Damian, you have only, I guess, 20
career kick returns, but, uh, your
numbers are are pretty pretty good in
that regard and you've had, uh, some
long returns. Is that something that uh
the Eagles talked to you about doing
here in Philadelphia?
>> I don't want to say talked about
specifically, but you know, it's always
on the table. You know, whatever I can
do to help this team win, whether it's
running the ball, returning the ball, or
just, you know, embracing any role that,
you know, Nick expects of me, you know,
um the conversation I had with, you
know, how it was just come here, have
fun, you know, just get acquainted to
the know, you know, the offense, get
acquainted to the city, man. We're just
going to see how it plays out.
We'll go to Rube and then Kaden.
>> You haven't um haven't played a whole
lot the last couple years. You had that
big game at the end of I guess 24
um against Tennessee. How tough has it
been to to not really play that much
over a couple year period?
>> Uh coming from an athletic standpoint,
you know, coming from, you know, just
being a competitor, you know, it sucks.
You know, it sucks. Just just bluntly
putting it. But, uh, like I said, I'm at
a point now in my career where I got
experience on my side and, um, I'm just
using it as a building block to go
further, man.
>> If no one else,
>> how'd you, if I could just follow up,
how'd you get through that the
frustrations?
>> Uh, just staying grounded and um,
looking at the end goal. You know, at
the end of the day, I'm an NFL football
player. You know, I'm doing what most
guys dream of. I'm doing what I've been
dreaming of ever since I was a little
kid, you know. So, that's enough motiv
motivation for me personally. But, uh,
in the heat of the moment, you know,
like I'm human, so, you know, of course
it's gonna be tough, but like I say, you
know, I found ways to persevere and, um,
I'm here in Philly ready to, you know,
get back on brand.
>> We'll go to Kaden and then Ed,
>> you mentioned, you know, wanting to to
get back to that high level of ball.
What What would it take for you to get
there? What's the key to kind of getting
back to that point you were, you know,
three years ago?
>> I think the thing that everybody would
agree on is consistency. you know,
whether that's taking care of my body,
whether that's playbook, whether that's,
you know, just staying after practice,
you know, whatever I got to do, I'm
gonna find my I just got to find it, you
know.
>> We'll finish with Ed here.
>> Yeah. Hey, Damian. Um, I've seen you
play some games in Houston and with
Florida. Uh, and you've always seemed
like you a very physical style of
runner. You run guys over. Do you still
play with that same style or have the
injuries changed maybe some of the way
you approach uh the way you run the
football?
>> No, I don't think so. I really don't
think so.
>> Still the same physical
>> pounder.
>> I would like to think so. I would like
to think so.
>> Yeah. It's funny because I asked you
about Barkley, but Tank Bixby kind of
plays that way, too. Are you familiar
with Tank Tank at all?
>> Yeah, I love his career at Arbor. seen
him a little bit in Jacksonville because
uh I was at Houston so he was our
conference opponent. Got to see a good
bit of him and uh in Jacksonville as
well and um of course I've been keeping
tabs on him in his career here at
Philly. He's a great running back, young
guy, promising and uh like I said, like
you mentioned earlier, you know, that
running back room just full of guys, you
know, just ready to compete and play
ball, man.
>> Do you feel your similar style to Tank
with the physicality? Do you feel that's
kind of a similarity that you two share?
would you say?
>> I don't want to say I'm like nobody, you
know. You know, Tank run his way, I run
my way. But, you know, in in that
regard, yes, I would agree that we're
both physical bats who use physicality,
you know, to get every yard we can. For
sure.
>> All right. Thank you. Thanks for the
time, Damian.
>> For sure. Thank y'all.